The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
4 months later
Valley above the
Immortal Graveyard
If I enter a spatial rift,
I will lose my anchor point to the outside.
But if I don't,
it will be difficult to find my avatar...
This person is bad news.
Fellow cultivator,
we don’t even know each other.
Why must you act like this ?!
There were 7 of you when you entered.
Why did only the two of you come out ?
I’ve never met him before
so why does he feel somewhat familiar ?
No answer ?
You can die then.
Senior,
among the other 5, there must be someone you know.
Junior admits her mistake.
After my father disappeared in the Immortal Graveyard
I was sold to the country of Suzaku.
I became a cultivation furnace,
living a life worse than death.
I refused to accept it
and luckily managed to escape.
That's when I met Elder Gongsun.
He didn’t abandon me
and has protected me ever since.
He was even willing to accompany me to the Immortal Graveyard
to search for traces of my father.
To divert the attention of the Forsaken Immortal Clan,
I used the Reincarnation Fruits as bait.
and invited 5 others to join me.
But I failed to find my father
so I had no choice but to leave.
Senior,
I was the one who hid the truth.
If Senior wants to kill someone,
then kill this Junior.
Don’t hurt Elder Gongsun.
Miss,
let him kill me.
I would rather die now
than live as someone's tattoo puppet.
Find Wang Lin
and I'll let you two live.
Impossible,
how could a furnace chosen by Suzaku
have escaped so easily ?
Gongsun Fan was clearly marked by a tattoo seed
yet he’s different from the others,
and they managed to escape unscathed.
There must be
someone else backing them.
I left drops of blood within their bodies
so that I can find my way.
A few days later
Senior...
I...
The thing is,
this was all your fault.
Wait !
This trip to the Immortal Graveyard was truly perilous.
Fortunately,
I obtained a Reincarnation Fruit needed for my body cleansing.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.
I have finally become
a true Ancient God.
3 years later
Our Apricot Village
is undergoing the Heaven's Path Sect's recruitment.
Son, listen carefully to what they say.
If any child is chosen
it will be a great honor for its family.
Yes !
Zhou Ru
5 years old
Next
None of them have Spirit Roots...
This kid,
I’ll take her.
Immortal,
this child is born mute.
No problem.
Thank you, Immortal
Ru’er,
bow to your master.
Hurry...
This child is so fortunate !
Innate spiritual energy,
all her meridians are opened,
and a purple aura.
Move faster, damn it !
If I miss the spirit stone exchange,
you’ll regret it !
Stupid girl !
I’ll beat you to death.
Do you dare ?
Senior...
I...
Wan’er...
Uncle
Can you speak ?
Would you like to cultivate with me ?
She will eventually step into cultivation world.
Since her parents can’t protect her,
I might as well take her with me
to ensure her safety.
Ceng Niu,
come out and fight me !
you have such a reputation
yet you hide in the valley, afraid to fight ?
Are you afraid of losing ?
We’re home.
Hungry ?
The chopsticks are flying !
Go ahead.
Why don't you eat ?
Once you reach a certain level of cultivation
you no longer need to eat.
I dreamed that my parents were gone.
Everything around me was pitch black.
Only...
Only I was left.
I’m here,
don’t be afraid.
What if you’re not here in the future ?
So shiny...
This is for you.
If you ever need me,
just shake it
and I’ll appear.
Wan’er...
Ceng Niu,
you coward !
Do you dare to come out and fight ?
Ceng Niu,
come out and fight me !
I’ll let you take one of my arms.
I’ll let you take both of my arms !
Attack !
You're noisy.
10-ingredients tonic soup
Come and take a look !
Do you like it ?
Dad, I want this !
Alright
It's delicious !
Slow down !
Uncle,
help me to capture this little pet.
If I hadn’t seen it with my own eyes,
I wouldn’t have believed Wan’er was like this.
5 years later
Uncle !
What's the matter ?
Wang Lin's avatar
Middle stage Soul Formation
Zhou Ru
10 years old
Nothing.
Little Ru'er,
hide in the pagoda.
Ceng Niu, come out !
Xue Ye’s Liao Fen is here
to ask for the feather fan back.
Liao Fan
Country of Xue Yue
Late stage Soul Formation
Ceng Niu,
I am here to settle the grudge
between you
and Xue Yue !
Kill !
If you are only this strong,
then you will
meet your end.
Today is the 17th of March.
Ceng Niu,
this is the day you die !
Sonic Wave Spirit Armor !
Which one of you bastards dared to hurt me ?
This voice...
Is this...
the chilling aura of the Underworld Ascension Method ?
Quickly find a Yin energy gathering location
to cultivate the Underworld Ascension Method.
Underworld Ice Flame ?
How do you know this technique ?
Who the hell are you ?
It wouldn't hurt to tell you,
my name is
Situ Nan !
Go away !
Situ Nan...
How could this be ?
Impossible...
Impossible !
Senior Situ,
if that really was your severed arm,
then I kind of believe what you said back then.
Note: "Suzaku" is the name of the country and planet
"the Suzaku" is the title of strongest individual on planet Suzaku
But the title of Suzaku's strongest person
is held by the one and only Suzaku.
Were you
really the Suzaku ?
Senior Situ,
the 10-year agreement is near.
My chances of winning this battle are slim
but there’s no avoiding it.
Little White,
look up !
Look down !
Fellow cultivator Ceng Niu,
The 10-year agreement is up.
Mount Suzaku ordered me
to escort you.
Tie Yan,
Yes ?
The Thunder Frog and the pagoda
will stay here.
No one can enter within a 100 li radius.
While I’m gone,
take good care of Little Ru’er for me.
Benefactor, don’t worry.
This old man will ensure the safety
of lady Ru’er.
Little Ru’er,
come here.
Bad Uncle !
You go out to play by yourself without taking Little Ru'er.
While I’m away,
listen to Uncle Tie Yan.
When I come back,
I’ll catch an even bigger tiger for you.
Really ?
Even bigger than Little White ?
Even bigger than Little White.
Okay,
but you have to come back quickly.
Uncle !
Uncle...
You must return safely...
Alright,
you also take care of yourself.
Master !
I’ve thoroughly investigated Ceng Niu’s strength
Tell me.
This Ceng Niu
is now at Middle stage Soul Formation.
His domain
seems to be the Life and Death reincarnation cycle.
He has a flying sword that can chop anything
Li Yuanfeng
Xue Yue's Suzerain
Early stage Soul Transformation
and a mysterious pagoda.
Not only that
but I used the treasure you gave me to test him
and he...
also masters the Underworld Ascension Method.
In the past,
he severed Red Butterfly’s arm.
And now,
he caught the attention of the Suzaku.
How could he be an ordinary person ?
So what you told me before,
do we forget about it ?
It’s not the right time yet,
I’ve already set up the trap.
After he fights Red Butterfly,
I’ll make my move.
Regardless of the outcome,
Ceng Niu
will die for sure.
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.